var questions = [
    {   
        question: "Which of the following is true about typeof operator in JavaScript",
        selection: [
        "document.location='http://www.newlocation.com';",
        "browser.location='http://www.newlocation.com';",
        " navigator.location='http://www.newlocation.com';",
        "window.location='http://www.newlocation.com';"
        ],
        answer: "window.location='http://www.newlocation.com';"
    },
    {   
        question: " Which built-in method returns the character at the specified index?",
        selection: [
        "characterAt()",
        "TgetCharAt()",
        "charAt()",
        "None of the above."
       ],
        answer: "charAt()"
    },
    {   
        question: "Which built-in method returns the calling string value converted to upper case?", 
        selection: [
        "toUpperCase()",
        "toUpper()",
        "changeCase(case)",
        "None of the above."
        ],
        answer: "toUpperCase()"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following function of Number object returns a string value version of the current number?",
        selection: [
        "toString()",
        "toFixed()",
        "toLocaleString()",
        "toPrecision()"],
        answer: "toString()"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following function of String object returns the characters in a string beginning at the specified location through the specified number of characters?",
        selection: [ 
        "slice()",
        "split()",
        "substr()",
        "search()"
        ],
        answer: "substr()"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following function of String object returns the primitive value of the specified object.",
        selection: [
        "toUpperCase()",
        "toString()",
        "toLocaleUpperCase()",
        "valueOf()"
        ],
        answer: "valueOf()"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following function of String object causes a string to be displayed as a subscript, as if it were in a <sub> tag?",
        selection: [
        "sup()", 
        "small()", 
        "strike()", 
        "sub()"
        ],
        answer: "sub()"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following function of Array object adds one or more elements to the end of an array and returns the new length of the array?",
        selection: [
        "pop()", 
        "push()", 
        "join()", 
        "map()"],
        answer: "push()"
    },
    {
        question: "10 - Which of the following function of Array object reverses the order of the elements of an array?",
        selection: [
        "reverse()", 
        "push()", 
        "reduce()", 
        "reduceRight()"
        ],
        answer: "reverse()"
    },
    {
        question: "TArrays in JavaScript can be used to store:---",
        selection: [
        "numbers and strings",
        "others Arrays",
        "booleances", 
        "all of the above"
        ],
        answer: "all of the above"
    },
    {
        question: "The condition in an if/else statement is enclosed within:---",
        selection: [
        "quotes",
        "Curly brackets",
        "parentheses", 
        "square brackets"
        ],
        answer: "parentheses"
    }

];


